[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 4 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "17",
        "20",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 6 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "41",
      "options": [
        "39",
        "46",
        "41",
        "43"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 5 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "47",
      "options": [
        "47",
        "52",
        "49",
        "45"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 8 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "97",
      "options": [
        "95",
        "97",
        "102",
        "99"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 4 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "12",
        "17",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 10 \u00d7 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "84",
      "options": [
        "89",
        "86",
        "82",
        "84"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 10 + 1 \u00d7 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "17",
      "options": [
        "19",
        "15",
        "17",
        "22"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 9 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "34",
      "options": [
        "39",
        "34",
        "32",
        "36"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 12 + 9 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "57",
      "options": [
        "57",
        "62",
        "59",
        "55"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 5 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "11",
        "6",
        "8"
      ]
    }
]